<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BIJournal</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="journal">Journal</string>
    <string name="collegium">Editorial Board</string>
    <string name="release">Release</string>
    <string name="prev_releases">Previous releases</string>
    <string name="for_authors">Authors guidelines</string>
    <string name="reviews">Peer reviewing</string>
    <string name="ethics">Publication ethics</string>
    <string name="subscription">Subscription</string>
    <string name="contacts">Contacts</string>
    <string name="for_authors_text">Articles should be topical and original, should outline tasks (issues), describe key results of the author’s research and appropriate conclusions.\n\nManuscripts are submitted via e-mail: bijournal@hse.ru.\n\nThe editors do not enter into discussions with the authors of rejected materials.\n\n\n<b>Manuscript requirements</b>\n\n<b>Text files</b> should be submitted in electronic form, as a MS Word document (version 2003 or higher).\n\n<b>Length. </b>Articles should be between 20 and 25 thousand characters (incl. spaces).\n\n<b>Font, spacing, margins.</b> The text should be in Times New Roman 12 pt, 1.5 spaced, fit to the width, margins: left – 25 mm, all other – 15 mm.\n\n<b>All the papers</b> should be submitted in English and/or in Russian. The accepted papers are published in the printed version of the journal in English, and in the electronic version – both in English and Russian (if necessary, translation is arranged by the journal).\n\n<b>Title</b> of the article should be submitted in native language and English.\n\n<b>Authors’ details</b> are presented in native language and English. The details include:\n    \u25CF  Full name of each author\n    \u25CF  Position, rank, academic degree of each author\n    \u25CF  Affiliation of each author, at the time the research was completed\n    \u25CF  Full postal address of each affiliation (incl. postcode / ZIP)\n    \u25CF  E-mail address of each author.\n\n<b>Abstract</b> are presented in native language and English.\n    \u25CF  The abstract should be between 200 and 300 words.\n    \u25CF  The abstract should be informative (no general words), original, relevant (reflects your paper’s key content and research findings); structured (follows the logics of results’ presentation in the paper)\n    \u25CF  The recommended structure: purpose (mandatory), design / methodology / approach (mandatory), findings (mandatory), research limitations / implications (if applicable), practical implications (if applicable), originality / value (mandatory).\n    \u25CF  It is appropriate to describe the research methods/methodology if they are original or of interest for this particular research. For papers concerned with experimental work the data sources and data procession technique should be described.\n    \u25CF  The results should be described as precisely and informatively as possible. Include your key theoretical and experimental results, factual information, revealed interconnections and patterns. Give special priority in the abstract to new results and long-term impact data, important discoveries and verified findings that contradict previous theories as well as data that you think have practical value.\n    \u25CF  Conclusions may be associated with recommendations, estimates, suggestions, hypotheses described in the paper.\n    \u25CF  Information contained in the title should not be duplicated in the abstract. Authors should try to avoid unnecessary introductory phrases (e.g. “the author of the paper considers…”).\n    \u25CF  Authors should use the language typical of research and technical documents to compile your abstract and avoid complex grammatical constructions.\n    \u25CF  The text of the abstract should include key words of the paper.\n\n\n<b>Keywords</b> are presented in native language and English. The number of key words / words combinations are from 6 to 10 (separated by semicolons).\n\n<b>Formulae</b> should be prepared using MS Equation tool.\n\n<b>Figures</b> should be of high quality, legible and numbered consecutively with Arabic numerals. All figures (charts, diagrams, etc.) should be submitted in electronic form (photo images – in TIF or JPEG formats, minimum resolution 300 dpi). Appropriate references in the text are required.\n\n<b>References</b> should be presented in Harvard style and carefully checked for completeness, accuracy and consistency.\n\n<b>The publication is free of charge.</b></string>
    <string name="more_info_about_collegium"><u>More about editorial board</u></string>
    <string name="reviewing_text">All the papers submitted for publication in «Business Informatics» journal are subject to reviewing and approval by the Editorial Board.\n\nThe manuscript submitted to the editors is subject to initial review and verification for compliance to the topics of the journal and formal editorial requirements. If the paper doesn’t comply with the subject-matter or formal requirements of the journal it excludes from further consideration, the author is notified about it.\n\nIf the paper is compliant with the topics and formal requirements is assigned for reviewing to an expert – a member of the Editorial Board (internal review). The paper can also be submitted for evaluation by an independent expert (external review).\n\nThe review process is anonymous both for the referee and for the author. The review results are provided by the referee in written form. The review should include general evaluation of the paper’s content and principal judgment on whether it could be published in the journal, specific enumeration of errors in the methodology and tools (if any), as well as recommendations for improving of the text.\n\nAccording to the reviewing results the paper may be accepted for publication, sent to the author for revision, or rejected.\n\nUpon receipt of a positive conclusion of the referee the paper is placed in the journal’s portfolio for further publication. Executive secretary of the Editorial Board informs the author about the acceptance of the paper. The final decision on the publication of the paper and approval of the total contents of the journal’s issue are adopted at a meeting of the editorial board.\n\nThe procedure for review and approval of papers is from one to two months, then articles are published in order of priority. The Editorial Board may decide on an extraordinary publication of the paper.\n\nUpon receipt of a negative conclusion of the reviewer the paper is discussed on the meeting of the Editorial Board working group, which makes a decision on rejection of the article or the need for further review by an independent expert. In case of paper’s rejection, an appropriate notification is sent to the author.\n\nPreparing an article for publication undertaken by the editors includes normal literary editing and fine-tuning of the text according to the internal editorial standards adopted for the journal. All the changes made by the editors are to be coordinated with the author.</string>
    <string name="reviewing_title"><b>Peer reviewing</b></string>
    <string name="glav_redaktor_title"><b>Editor-in-Chief: Alexey Golosov</b></string>
    <string name="glav_redaktor_text">President of FORS Development Center, Russian Federation.  </string>
    <string name="zam_glav_redaktora_title"><b>Deputy Editor-in-Сhief</b></string>
    <string name="zam_glav_redaktora_text"><b>Svetlana Maltseva</b> – Professor, Head of Department of Innovation and Business in Information Technologies, National Research University Higher School of Economics, Russian Federation.\n\n<b>Yevgeni Koucheryavy</b> – Professor of Department of Electronics and Communication Engineering, Tampere University of Technology, Finland.</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="contacts_address_title">Address:</string>
    <string name="contacts_address">Shabolovka St, 26, Moscow, 119049, Russian Federation.</string>
    <string name="contacts_phone_title">Tel./fax:</string>
    <string name="contacts_phone">+7 (495) 771&#8211;32&#8211;38</string>
    <string name="contacts_site_title">Website:</string>
    <string name="contacts_site">http://bi.hse.ru/</string>
    <string name="contacts_email_title">E-mail:</string>
    <string name="contacts_email">bijournal@hse.ru</string>
    <string name="bi_magazine_title">Scientific journal\nBusiness Informatics</string>
    <string name="glav_redaktor_title1">Editor-in-Chief:\n Alexey Golosov</string>
    <string name="main_page_text">Business Informatics is a peer reviewed interdisciplinary academic journal published since 2007 by National Research University – Higher School of Economics (HSE), Moscow, Russian Federation. The journal is administered by the School of Business Informatics. The journal is issued quarterly; each paper is published in two languages – English and Russian.\n\nThe mission of the journal is to develop business informatics as a new field within both information technologies and management. It provides dissemination of latest technical and methodological developments, promotes new competences and provides a framework for discussion in the field of application of modern IT solutions in business, management and economics.</string>
    <string name="prev_release">Current release:</string>
    <string name="read">Read</string>
    <string name="subscription_title">Subscription</string>
    <string name="author_demands"><u>Authors guidelines</u></string>
    <string name="ethics_title">Publication ethics</string>
    <string name="ethics_text">The journal is committed to upholding the standards of publication ethics and takes all possible measures against any publication malpractices. Editors of the journal reserve the right to reject the work from publication in case of revealing any such malpractices.\n\n<b>Copyright</b>\n\nArticles submitted to the journal should not have been published before in their current or substantially similar form, or be under consideration for publication with another journal. All authors submitting their works acknowledge that they have disclosed all and any actual or potential conflicts of interest regarding authorship and publication of the work and will indemnify the publisher against any breach of such warranty. For ease of dissemination and to ensure proper policing of use, papers and contributions become the legal copyright of the publisher unless otherwise agreed.\n\n<b>Permissions</b>\n\nPrior to article submission, authors should clear permission to use any content that has not been created by them. Failure to do so may lead to lengthy delays in publication. The editors are unable to publish any article which has permissions pending. The rights we require are:\n\u2022 non-exclusive rights to reproduce the material in the article or book chapter;\n\u2022 print and electronic rights;\n\u2022 rights to use the material for the life of the work (i.e. there should be no time restrictions on the re-use of material e.g. a one-year license).\n\nWhen reproducing tables, figures or excerpts (of more than 400 words) from another source, it is expected that:\n\u2022 authors obtain the necessary written permission in advance from any third party owners of copyright for the use in print and electronic formats of any of their text, illustrations, graphics, or other material, in their manuscript. Permission must also be cleared for any minor adaptations of any work not created by them;\n\u2022 if an author adapts significantly any material, the author must inform the copyright holder of the original work;\n\u2022 authors obtain any proof of consent statements;\n\u2022 authors must always acknowledge the source in figure captions and refer to the source in the reference list;\n\u2022 authors should not assume that any content which is freely available on the web is free to use. Authors should check the website for details of the copyright holder to seek permission for re-use.\n\n<b>Verbatim copying</b>\nVerbatim copying of more than 10 per cent of another person’s work without acknowledgement, references or the use of quotation marks.\n<b>Paraphrasing</b>\nImproper paraphrasing of another person’s work is where more than one sentence within a paragraph or section of text has been changed or sentences have been rearranged without appropriate attribution. Significant improper paraphrasing (more than 10 per cent of a work) without appropriate attribution is treated as seriously as verbatim copying.\n\n<b>Re-using parts of a work without attribution</b>\nRe-use of elements of another person\'s work, for example a figure, table or paragraph without acknowledgement, references or the use of quotation marks. It is incumbent on the author to obtain the necessary permission to reuse elements of another person\'s work from the copyright holder.\n\n<b>Self plagiarism</b>\nOur requirement is that all authors sign a copyright form that clearly states that their submitted work has not been published before. If elements of a work have been previously published in another publication the author is required to acknowledge the earlier work and indicate how the subsequent work differs and builds upon the research and conclusions contained in the previous work. Verbatim copying of an author’s own work and paraphrasing is not acceptable and we recommend that research should only be reused to support new conclusions.\n\nWe recommend that authors cite all previous stages of publication and presentation of their ideas that have culminated in the final work, including conference papers, workshop presentations and listserv communications.\n\n<b>Handling allegations of plagiarism</b>\n\nThe editors seek to uphold academic integrity and to protect authors’ moral rights. We take all cases of plagiarism very seriously being aware of the potential impact an allegation of plagiarism can have on a researcher’s career. Therefore, we have procedures in place to deal with alleged cases of plagiarism.\n\nIn order for us to take an unbiased approach, we investigate each case thoroughly, seeking clarification from all affected parties.\n\nIf we are approached by a third party with an allegation of plagiarism, we would always seek a response from the original author(s) or copyright holder(s) before we decide on a course of action. We will not be influenced by other parties and will form our decisions in an unbiased and objective manner.\n\nEditors are not obliged to discuss individual cases of alleged plagiarism with third parties. We reserve the right not to proceed with a case if the complainant presents a false name or affiliation or acts in an inappropriate or threatening manner towards editorial staff.</string>
    <string name="subscription_text">You can subscribe to the journal in any post office of «Pochta Rossii» («Post of Russia»).\nOur subscription indexes in the «Rospechat» catalogue – 72315 in Russian and 80870 in English\n\nThe journal is published quarterly.\n\nContact us\33, Kirpichnaya str., Moscow, 105187, Russian Federation.\nTel./fax: +7 (495) 771&#8211;32&#8211;38\nE-mail: bijournal@hse.ru\n\nElectronic versions of the journal can be downloaded at http://bi.hse.ru/.</string>
    <string name="view_prev_releases"><u>View previous releases</u></string>
    <string name="created_by">Бизнес в стиле</string>
    <string name="switch_lang">English version</string>
</resources>
